eazel.com 2001-04-05

# Privacy Statement

| 

Eazel is dedicated to providing unsurpassed software products and services, and we rely upon you, our users, for our continued success. We recognize that your use of our Web site and software is, in part, an act of trust in our handling of any personal information you may provide us with. We appreciate that trust and will uphold the highest standards of online privacy and security to safeguard that information. 

In short, Eazel assures that 

  * We will ask you how you would like us to communicate with you, if at all. 
  * We will disclose how we will use our customer information, by detailing it in this document or through contact with Eazel. 
  * We will never sell customer information without making it clear that we may do so. 

Read on to find a detailed account of Eazel's Privacy Policy. Please feel free to contact us at [info@eazel.com](mailto:info@eazel.com) if you have any questions regarding this policy. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Use, available at http://www.eazel.com/aboutus/terms_of_use, and represents our commitment to the privacy and proper security of your information. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time as our products and services change and expand. You are encouraged to periodically review this policy, as your continued use of this site and Eazel software will signify your acceptance of these new terms. 

**Our Products and Services**   
Eazel's Nautilus shell, an innovative network user environment, along with Internet-based services are designed to make computers easier and more enjoyable to use. In order to achieve this goal and to provide advanced solutions, Eazel does require some personally identifiable information from you, and some aggregate data, as discussed below. 

**Information Collected**   
During registration for Nautilus download and Eazel Services, we may require you to submit contact information, such as an email address, and unique identifiers, such as a password. Unique identifiers are collected to verify your identity and are used as account numbers in our record system. Other personally identifiable information, such as your name, physical address, phone number, zip code, gender, and so on, are optional. 

As part of the Eazel Services registration process, you may have the opportunity to provide a system profile. The system profile consists of 

1\. An inventory of the Red Hat Package Manager files installed on the system. This information helps us determine what new software updates may be valuable to you in keeping your system secure and available. 

2\. An inventory of your system hardware and certain configuration files. This information also helps us determine what software and support information may be useful to you. 

Once you have registered a system profile, you can browse this profile through Nautilus or from our Web site. 

Other than as described in 1 and 2 above, Eazel will never retrieve or store personal file information from your system as part of any Eazel service. 

Eazel's Web site automatically tracks the IP-host address of a browser to help us track usage, data flow, and so on, and similarly tracks downloads of software from our site. This information is collected anonymously, meaning that it is not associated with any personally identifiable information we have from you. 

Eazel's Web site also uses cookies - small bits of information stored by your Internet browser on your computer's hard disk - to track what pages you view, what search terms you enter, what ads you click on, and so on. All this information is collected anonymously and is not traceable to you. 

Finally, when you initially install and first launch Eazel software, it will communicate back to a central server. This is for configuration purposes, and no personally identifiable information is exchanged between the software and the server. 

**How That Information Is Used**   
Eazel uses information collected during registration, including your contact information, solely to communicate with you. The optional demographic data we ask for is for internal research-and-marketing purposes. For those users who subscribe, Eazel will periodically distribute a newsletter containing information on the status of Eazel products and services. 

We use information we collect through our use of cookies to track your identity through a session (so that you don't have to reenter information in every page) as well as for research-and-marketing purposes. 

Please note the following: 

  * Client Software  
The Eazel desktop client software, or Nautilus, may need to perform diagnostics on your system in order to retrieve information regarding installed software and hardware, and to provide updates, solutions to problems, or other value-added services. Eazel will use the data collected through the client software only to generate a statement to you and to deliver subscribed services from Eazel or affiliated third parties. Eazel may also anonymously aggregate this data to help us determine what services may be most valuable to our customers. 
  * Online Storage   
The Eazel file-storage service provides online storage of files for access from both the Eazel desktop client software, Nautilus, and through the Web site. The service may provide space for a Private Folder and Public Folder. The Private Folder will rely on user authentication for access and hence will be limited to use only by the specified owner of the service subscription. The Public Folder, however, may be available to other users or to the entire general public, and Eazel does not provide any privacy on these files beyond what you have selected as options for those folders. 

When using the Public Folder, you acknowledge that you are sharing data with other registered users and are restricted from sharing any illegal or copyrighted material as outlined in the Terms of Use. Eazel places no security or privacy guarantees on this data, placing uploading and downloading of shared data at your discretion. 

**Is Information Shared With or Disclosed to Third Parties?**   
Aggregate data - that is, data Eazel collects anonymously which is not linked to your personally identifiable information - may be shared with Eazel's advertisers or affiliates for advertising, marketing, or research purposes. We may use third parties to help us create and manage our products and services. If we need to disclose personally identifiable information for these functions, we require that the third parties use it only for the purpose for which it was disclosed. Otherwise, Eazel will disclose personally identifiable information to third parties only as required by law, pursuant to a validly executed search warrant or subpoena, or as Eazel believes is necessary to avoid liability or losses by Eazel or users of its software and services.

Should Eazel be acquired or transfer a business unit that uses personally identifiable information to another company, the information related to the transferred or acquired business will be available to the new combined company. In the unlikely event that Eazel ceases operations, we cannot predict with certainty what would occur. However, we reserve the right to transfer all our user data to another company that offers similar or related products and services. Our hope is that we can allow you to receive some continuity of service and support. 

**Security**   
Eazel uses appropriate technologies to ensure the security of user information and data within Nautilus and Eazel Services. Members communicate with Eazel Services over an encrypted Secure Sockets Layer channel. The Web browser authenticates the Eazel server with a VeriSign public-key certificate. You authenticate through an Eazel-signed public-key certificate, providing a user name and password to authenticate to Eazel Services, which are always communicated over an encrypted SSL connection. The integrity information of the downloaded packages is received over the SSL connection in order to ensure integrity and authenticity.

**Advertising**   
Eazel uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads to the Eazel Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to understand your choices regarding this issue, visit [www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy/default.asp?asp_object_1=&](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy/default.asp?asp_object_1=&)

**Children's Online Privacy Protection**  
Eazel, its Web site and its software are not directed to children under the age of 13. Eazel prohibits registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. 

**Public Forums**   
Eazel may provide public user forums such as discussion groups, message boards, and newsgroups to users. All information disclosed by you on these forums is, by default, public information, and you should exercise care when disclosing information in these venues. 

**Links**  
Eazel may provide links to other Web sites from within the client software, services, or the corporate site. Eazel does not ensure privacy on sites that are owned or operated by other companies, and we caution you to read the individual privacy statements for these sites. 

|  |
